《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously, on "The Flash"...
-是个武士  -叫闪电侠来见我
- It's a Samurai. - Bring me the Flash.
不然你的城市就完蛋了
Or else, your city falls.
巴里还困在神速力里呢
Barry's still stuck in the Speed Force?
我要把他弄出来  我需要你帮助
I'm gonna get him out. But I need your help.
巴里  是我  爱瑞丝
Barry? It's me, Iris.
吵  草  恼
Loud, cloud, proud.
回到我身边吧
Please come back to me.
巴里  爱瑞丝有危险
Barry, Iris is in trouble.
闪电侠回来了
Flash is back!
闪电侠  欢迎回来
Flash... welcome home.
闪电侠回到中城了
The Flash is back in Central City.
闪电侠回归
你回到我身边了
You came back to me.
我再也不会离开你了
I'm never going anywhere ever again.
不仅可以买到这座
Not only is this the most modern,
豪华的顶层公寓
lavish penthouse on the market,
还可以收获中城最好的景色
it also has one of the best views in all of Central City.
跟我去阳台  你可以亲眼看看
Join me on the balcony. See for yourself.
我根本不关心什么风景
I couldn't care less about the view.
这是最贵的了吗
Is it your most expensive listing?
是的  不过价格可以再商量
Yes, but the price is negotiable.
我要了
I'll take it.
太棒了
Yes.
我锁一下门  然后和你下去
Just, let me lock up and I'll ride down with you.
抱歉  我不知道该按哪个键
Sorry, not sure which button does what.
混蛋
Shmuck.
该死
Damn it.
丹娜  听我说
Dana? Yeah, listen.
我被困在电梯里了
I think I'm in some busted elevator or some--
我不知道该
I don't know...
基尔戈
不
No!
闪 电 侠
第四季
第二集
什么
What?
不
No!
巴里
Barry.
你起得挺早
Hi, you're up early.
看什么呢
Doing what, exactly?
我是补一下被困在神速力里面
I'm just catching up on all the TV I missed
这段时间所落下的电视节目
while I was stuck in the Speed Force.
离开半年的世界
When you've been gone six months,
到处都是剧透
the world is a minefield of spoilers.
不过西斯科帮我
But Cisco hooked me up
把我最喜欢的节目
with the 1,000-times sped up version
用1000倍快进的速度播放
of my favorite shows.
琼恩·雪诺死了  他又活了
Jon Snow died. Oh, he's alive!
原来我还以为你是
And here I was thinking you'd need a jump start
-榆木脑袋呢  -不是
- for your loopy brain. - Nope.
脑袋很好  我一切都很好
Brain good. All of me is good.
乔需要我  去案发现场
Joe needs me. Crime scene.
好的  或许我应该开始考虑
Oh, that's okay. I should probably get started
被我们遗忘的婚礼计划了
on our neglected wedding plans.
我得花好久的时间
It's gonna take me forever
才能看完这些材料  所以
to get through this binder, so...
别担心这事了
Oh, no. Don't worry about it.
我已经搞定了
I'm done with it.
-你搞定了  -是的
- You're done? - Yeah.
我确定了餐饮服务商  买了你最喜欢的花
I locked in a caterer, I got you your favorite flowers,
预定了一个景色非常好的地方
I put a deposit on a venue with an amazing view,
还定了七层桑椹巧克力蛋糕
I got that seven tier raspberry chocolate cake.
看来你把一切都弄好了
Well, I guess you've got everything covered.
这样我可爱的未婚妻就不用紧张了
So, my lovely fiancee can remain stress-free.
给我留一块熊爪蛋糕
Save me a bear claw?
不能保证哦  极速者
Ooh, no promises, speedster.
你跑掉了  就啥都没了
You whoosh, you lose.
什么情况  乔
What do we got, Joe?
有用的消息不多
Not much to go off.
唯一的目击证人是位住在这的老年人
The only witness was an elderly resident, and...
她还惊魂未定
she's still pretty rattled.
艾伦先生
Mr. Allen.
你迟到了半年零五分钟
Six months and five minutes late.
抱歉  辛格队长
Sorry, Captain Singh.
再次感谢批准了我的延长休假
Thank you again for granting me that extended sabbatical.
不过我现在回来了  准备好工作了
But I'm back, I'm ready to work,
今天是多美好的一天啊
and what can I say-- it's a beautiful day.
抱歉  这次是什么案子
Sorry. What are we dealing with?
希望你早饭没有吃太多
Well, I hope you had a light breakfast.
没有  我消化得很好
No, I had a good spread actually.
薄煎饼  香肠  水果麦片
Pancakes, sausage, fruity cereal...
到处都是  他
He's... everywhere.
据我们所知
As far as we can tell,
电梯是从一百多层掉下来的
it dropped him a hundred stories.
能查到受害者的身份吗
Were you able to ID the vic?
能  科特·韦弗
Yeah. Kurt Weaver.
身价亿万  超级有钱
Worth billions. Capital B.
你怎么看  艾伦先生
What do you think, Mr. Allen?
看到天花板上的碰撞了吗
You see the impacts on the ceiling?
还有边框重复的侧向应力龟裂
And the repeated lateral stress fissures on the frame?
这家伙不只坠落而死的  他是
This guy didn't just drop. He was...
被震死的
shaken to death.
抱歉  借过一下
Excuse me. Coming through.
中城警局科技顾问  没错
CCPD Tech Consultant. That's right.
看看警徽  这可是正式的
Look at the badge. That means it's official.
他知道那警徽是塑料的吧
He's aware that badge is plastic, right?
各位  很抱歉我迟到了
Fellas, so sorry I'm late.
今早这卷发完全不听话
The curls were not cooperating this morning.
老天  为什么给我看这些
Oh, good Lord. Why would you show me that?
我们认为这是因为某些技术故障
We think this is because of some weird technical glitch,
你是我们怪胎技术专家
and you're our weird tech expert.
这下可毁了我对是拉差辣椒酱的印象
This completely ruins Sriracha for me.
我来了
Yoink.
不应该啊
That shouldn't be there.
怎么了
What is it?
加密代码
It's encrypted code.
这不是故障事件  而是系统被人黑了
This wasn't a glitch. This was a hacker.
表层控制室的量子算法
The Cortex's quantum algorithm
应该很快就能破解这个代码
should decrypt this code in no time.
就能帮我们查到新黑客的身份
That should help us ID our new hacker.
在我们等待结果的同时
But while we wait,
我有些欢迎回归礼物要送给你
I got a little welcome back gift for you.
来来  跟我来
Come, come. Walk with ya boy.
大家都围过来  同志们
Gather round, class.
闪亮登场
Ka-blam!
你刚刚揭布的动作酷毙了
I mean, that was cool-- reveal and everything,
但是战衣我看过了
but I've seen that suit.
-其实我已经穿过了  -嗯
- I've actually already worn it. - Yeah.
我们都知道你把巴里的战衣好好地改造了一番
We all know you gave Barry's suit a nice little fancy makeover.
但不知道的事  你们还是不知道
Yeah, but you don't know what you don't know.
在这件红色战衣之下
And underneath all this red beautiful,
我装入了自动修复
I've built in self-repairing armor,
纳米液电路  全光谱扫瞄
nano-liquid circuitry, full-spectrum scanning,
还有其他一大堆专业名词
and a whole bunch of other big words.
但是最重要的是
Chief among them....
战衣技术控制
为你私人度身定制的显示器
Your very own custom-made HUD.
这东西装载着地图  电路表  外卖单
This thing is loaded with maps, schematics, delivery menus.
你知道你超喜欢的那家泰国菜吗
You know that Thai place you like so much?
超喜欢泰式炒河粉
Yeah, love the Pad See Ew.
你知道泰式炒河粉有多好吃
You know how we Pad See do.
兄弟  太棒了  这还能做什么
Dude, this is awesome. What else does it do?
你走运了
Well, lucky for you,
我还给你写了使用说明书
I even wrote you an instruction manual.
好棒
Yay.
拜托  现代人还需要说明书吗
Come on. We're not cavemen.
干得漂亮
Really good work.
当然
I know!
说明书我晚点再看
I'll look at this later.
我要回中城警局了
Um, I gotta get back to CCPD.
你可以怪在西斯科身上
And you can blame this on Cisco,
但我在想今晚吃泰国菜吧
but I'm thinking Thai tonight?
宝贝  说真的  晚上培训课程结束后
Ooh... honestly, babe, I'll probably be too tired
我也许会累到吃不下饭了
to eat out after our evening training session, so--
我取消了  不用担心
I cancelled that. Yeah, don't worry about that.
你取消了
You cancelled it?
是的  我觉得我们不需要
Yeah, I mean, I don't think we need it, right?
而且我回来了  我会预约的
Besides, I'm back. I'll make a reservation, okay?
巴里回来的感觉肯定很好吧
Must be so nice having Barry back.
是的
Yeah. Yes, it is.
但是
But...
他只是还需要一段时间
Well, I mean, it's just gonna take some time for him
来适应这里的新力度变化而已
to get used to the new dynamics around here, that's all.
嗯
Yeah.
在我和罗尼从一般同事
You know, when Ronnie and I went from just working together
到搭档工作  再到约会
to working together and dating,
我们在交流方面也遇到过麻烦
we had some trouble communicating.
我和巴里的交流没问题
Oh, I mean, Barry and I communicate just fine.
我只是这么说
Yeah, I'm-I'm just saying,
其实我们去看过情侣心理治疗
we actually went to couples therapy
真的很有帮助
and it really helped a lot.
谢谢你的建议  凯特琳  真的
I appreciate the advice, Caitlin-- really, I do.
但是你知道  我和巴里从小就认识到现在
But, you know, Barry and I have known each other since childhood.
我们真的不需要去看心理治疗
You know? We don't need therapy.
我是说
I mean...
我们是天生的一对
we're Barry and Iris, right?
好吧
Right.
但是谢谢你  而且
Thanks, though, I mean, you know,
我并不抗拒心理治疗  只是
I don't have anything against it, it's just...
你们是天生的一对  懂了
You're Barry and Iris. Gotcha.
有人擅自进入缺口  我们要行动了
Unauthorized breach incoming. We gotta move.
别变  别变  别变  别变
Don't change, don't change, don't change, don't change...
凯瑟琳  咱们走
Caitlin, let's go.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
一切就绪
For anything.
别开火
Hold your fire!
你下次能提前跟我说一声吗
Hey, you wanna give me a little more notice next time?
可是有想要杀我们的人从这里出来呢
You know, people who wanna kill us come through here, right?
是我的错  大家好
Oh. My bad, guys.
西斯科  你还挺英勇的  这么跳到前边
Cisco, that was very heroic of you to just jump in
保护吉普赛  真让人刮目相看
and protecting Gypsy like that. It's pretty impressive.
老兄  我是保护你们的
Dude, I'm protecting you from her.
她可是能把你们蒸发掉的
She would've vaporized you guys.
他可没撒谎
He's not lying.
收回你的话吧
As you were.
好了
Okay.
那么  你就快准备好我们的约会了吗
So, you almost ready for our date?
是啊  快了
Uh, yeah, almost. Um...
我试着解锁这个黑客密码时遇到了困难
I hit a snag in trying to decrypt this hacker code
中城警局的活  你知道我们行动方式
for the CCPD--I mean, you know how we do, and just,
就是有点像黑客帝国  你一点也不在乎
kind of, like, the matrix-you care about none of this.
给我一个小时  最多两小时
Just give me, like, one hour. Two tops.
然后...
And then...
就是你我二人时间了  保证
It's you and me. Promise.
你应该庆幸自己这么可爱
You're lucky you are so cute.
而你是最棒的
And you are amazing.
是啊
Yeah.
而且你关于可爱那一点可是说的太对了
And you're so right about that cute thing too.
去去就来
B-r-b.
好
Okay.
基尔戈
警告
伙计们  有辆车开到120还来回并线
Guys? There's a car going 120 swerving between lanes.
肯定会撞死人的
Somebody's gonna get killed.
你们俩都得去
You both need to get out there.
就一辆车  交给我吧
That's one car. I got it.
但是我...
Yeah, but I--
我可以帮你
I can help you.
救命  救命
Help! Help!
各位  是车辆失控  司机困在里边
Okay, guys, it's a runaway. Driver's trapped inside.
我去改变他的行进路线
I'm gonna change his trajectory.
好  让他向左拐
Okay, then turn him left.
那里有个阻挡失控车辆的
There's a turn-off for runaway trucks coming up.
把路清开  车就能安全停在那里了
Just clear a path and the car will come to a safe stop there.
不不  我可以把他推到右边
No, no, no. I'm gonna push him right.
那条街是空的  我可以在那里帮他
That street's empty. I can help him there.
巴里  你不能走那条路
Barry, you can't go down that road.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
因为他们三个月前
Because they started construction
在那条街开始施工了
on that street three months ago.
不要  不要  不要
No, no, no, no, no, no.
我知道有个人差点死了
I know a guy almost died,
但是今天发生在这性感猛兽身上的事
but what happened to this sexy beast here today
才是真正的悲剧
is the real tragedy.
它的下场可能会更糟
That could've been a lot worse.
真抱歉  各位  这都是我的错
I'm sorry, guys. This one is all on me.
我爸爸和司机蒂姆·权聊了下
Okay, so my dad talked to the driver, Tim Kwon.
他没事  他们要审讯他
He's fine. He's gonna question him
看看能不能找出是谁干的
and see if they can figure out who did this.
西斯科  有什么发现吗
Cisco? What do we got?
立刻开始汽车尸检
Beginning auto-topsy. Now.
这个和电梯杀人现场的奇怪代码一样
That is the same weird code from the elevator murder scene.
等下  这是不是意味着
Wait, doesn't that mean...
我们这黑客有个刺杀名单
Our hacker's got a hit list.
什...  你能破解吗
Wa--can you crack it?
老兄  我一整天都在破解这代码
Man, I've been trying to crack this code all day.
它看起来像是个病毒
It looks like a virus.
是啊  因为这是个电脑病毒
Well, yeah, because it's a computer virus.
不不  让开
No, no, no. Scooch.
我感觉到被侵犯了
Oh. I feel violated.
看起来像是有机体病毒
It looks like an organic virus.
但底基层确实数码构成的
But with a digital sub-base.
我们的杀手不仅仅是黑进机器
Our killer isn't just hacking machines.
他在控制他们
He's controlling them.
我们的黑客不是个黑客
Our hacker's not a hacker.
他是超能力者
He's a meta.
两名受害者之间有联系吗
Is there any connection between the two victims?
网上什么都没有
There's nothing online.
但是他们的名字  韦弗  权
But their names--Weaver, Kwon-
我听起来很耳熟
they sound very familiar to me.
我高中的时候开始收集科技杂志
I started collecting these tech magazines in high school.
-他们好像是...  -你上高中的时候
- They were like- - Those are the magazines
收集的是那种杂志吗
you collected in high school?
好吧  这话说得有点伤人
Okay. That's--that's hurtful.
真的挺伤人的  不过
That's really hurtful. Anyway.
我百分之九十确定在其中读到过这些名字
I'm 90% sure that's where I read those names.
那太好了  开始调查吧
Okay, great. Start digging.
巴里  我能和你谈一下吗
Barry, can I talk to you for a second?
关于刚才发生的事  我很抱歉
Hey, about what happened- I am sorry.
我应该听你的  就只是
I should've listened to you, it's just,
有时候我在外边  一切发生的都太快
sometimes when I'm out there, things move so fast
我真的很激动自己又成为了闪电侠
and I'm really excited to be the Flash again.
不过  希望你别生气
Anyway, I hope you're not mad.
但是你还是生气了  对吧
And you are. You're mad, aren't you?
不不  我没有生气
No, no. I'm not mad.
我只是觉得  我们既然订婚了
I just think with-- with us being engaged
现在还一起工作
and now we're working together,
那我们就更应该好好沟通了
that it's more important than ever that we communicate.
我完全同意
I completely agree.
很好  因为之前凯特琳提到过
Good, because Caitlin mentioned something earlier
但我没当一回事  可现在我...
and I sort of dismissed it, but now I'm--
我真觉得这样可以帮到我们
I'm really thinking that it could help us.
是什么
What is it?
情侣心理治疗
Couples therapy.
Couples therapy?
-对  -你...
- Mm-hmm. - You...
我们俩之间不是有问题吧
We're not, like, in trouble, are we?
不不  当然没有
No, no. No, of course not.
我只是觉得任何
I just think that any couple
像我们这样的情侣  最好
that's doing everything we're doing could
多接受些建议
use some advice.
我们只是要调整一下  这...
We're just talking about a tune up, I mean, there's--
没什么毛病  对吧
there's nothing wrong with that, right?
调整  对对  不  我是说
A tune up? Right, yeah, no, I mean,
如果这是你想要做的
if it's--sure, if it's what you wanna do,
-那我们就这么做  -太好了
- then sure, yeah, let's try it. - Great.
因为我的预约在半小时后
'Cause we've got an appointment in 30 minutes.
我去拿钱包
I'll get my purse.
什么
What?
奎恩市长就是绿箭侠
一会再跟你解释
Later.
-你好  是爱瑞丝吗  -你好
- Hi. Iris? - Hi.
-巴里  -你好
- Barry? - Hello.
你们好  我是莎伦·芬科尔医生
Hi, I'm Doctor Sharon Finkel.
抱歉让你们等我
I am so sorry I kept you waiting.
不不  没事的
Oh, no, no. It's fine.
谢谢你把我们安排进来
Thank you for squeezing us in.
电话里你说得很紧急的样子
Oh, well, you made it sound so urgent on the phone.
不不
No.
不紧急
No, not urgent.
我等不及要开始了
I'm excited to dive in.
对吧
Right?
当然  我喜欢心理治疗
Oh, absolutely. I love therapy.
你们之前接受过心理治疗吗
Oh. Have you been before?
小时候有过一次
Just once, when I was a kid,
在我母亲过世后
after my mom died.
你的母亲
Oh, your mom. Oh.
但现在没事了
But I'm okay with that.
也并不是没事  很明显
I mean, I'm not okay with it, obviously.
我更希望她还活着
I mean, I'd prefer that she was alive.
我的意思只是我能处理好这些了
I just meant that I've already dealt with it is--
我不觉得这些有必要写下来
I don't think it's worth writing down.
这些笔记是写给我自己看的
These notes are just for me.
没有人会评价你们
No one is judging you guys.
我们了解
Yes, we know.
对了  我父亲也过世了
Oh, my dad died too.
你也可以记下来
Just for your notes.
巴里  之前在电话里  爱瑞丝
So, Barry, Iris filled me in a little bit
跟我说了一下你们俩的情况
about the two of you on the phone before.
-要结婚了  -对
- Getting married? - Yeah.
是的  走到这一步经历了很多
Yeah, it's been a long road getting here.
首先
First, um...
我们从小一起长大  然后
us growing up together, and then, um,
我和另一个人订婚了
I was engaged to someone else.
知道了
Oh, okay.
这也有必要写下来吗
That's worth a write-down?
那家伙也死了
He's actually dead too.
你们俩经历过很多创伤啊
Oh, you two have had to deal with a lot of trauma.
-这...  -不 不是...
- Well... - No, not a...
-艾迪  还有罗尼  -是有点吧
- Eddie...and Ronnie. - I mean, a little.
-我妈妈  HR  -也不是很多
- My mom. H.R. - Not too much.
-劳蕾尔  -是有一些吧
- Laurel. - Some.
-史纳特  -我们参加过一些葬礼
- Snart. - We've been to a few funerals.
是的
Yeah.
巴里
So, Barry,
你觉得爱瑞丝为什么希望你俩今天来见我
why do you think Iris wanted you two to see me today?
爱瑞丝和我...
Well, Iris and I--
我们最近开始一起工作
we recently started working together.
我之前离开了一阵子
You see, I went away for a while on a, uh...
-出差去了  -出差
- A business trip. - Business trip.
走了半年  我猜现在
For six months and y-- um, I guess now--yeah.
我们在慢慢调整回之前的状态
We're just learning to get back in sync,
再次适应彼此
to sync up again.
对吗
Is that right?
这没有什么对错  巴里
Well, there's no right or wrong, Barry.
对
Right.
我觉得我们应该更注意彼此倾听
I think we could work on listening a little bit more.
-对吧  -对
- Right? - Uh-huh, yeah.
不然另一方会很受伤
Um, or else, someone could get really hurt.
比方说
You know, like, if they crashed their car
就像一百迈的车撞上了一堵墙
into a brick wall going 100 miles per hour.
她就是打个比方
She means that emotionally.
是吗
Do I?
你好  我的美人
Hello, mamacita.
他们把你做的都不像你了
They don't make them like you anymore.
这是在干嘛
What the hell?
别生气  这只是《每月主板》
Easy, it's just the Motherboard of the Month,
07年七月那版  看看她
July of '07, okay? Look at her.
那要真是个女人就好了
Kinda wish it was a girl.
亲爱的  都过去几个小时了
Baby, it's been hours.
你们还没有什么进展吗
You guys haven't made any progress yet?
没有地方提到科特·韦弗或是蒂姆·权
No mention of Kurt Weaver or Tim Kwon
或是他俩之间的任何关系
or any connection between the two of them.
找到了  就是他
Until now. Got him.
快记下  伙计们  不然就没意义了
Take note, people, it's only hoarding if it doesn't pay off.
好吧  那这就是蒂姆·权
Okay, so that's Tim Kwon.
这是科特·韦弗  这是希拉·阿娜妮
That's Kurt Weaver. That's Sheila Agnani.
2014年南休斯顿地区经济贡献奖得主
这人是谁
Who's that guy?
抱歉撞到你了
Ooh, sorry about that.
没事  是我的错
No, it's definitely my fault.
防爆小组军械库
你完全想不到谁想害你吗
You don't have any idea who would wanna do you harm?
连一点猜想都没有吗
Not even a gut feeling?
没有  我觉得大家都爱亿万富翁不是吗
No, I mean, everyone loves a billionaire, right?
没有  我不知道
No, I have no idea.
手榴弹  大家快跑
Grenade! Everybody move!
那么  这次过来的目的是什么
So, what would you say your goals are for this session?
我只是想知道巴里能了解到
Uh, well, I just want to know that Barry hears my concerns
我对我们之间沟通问题的担心
about our issues with miscommunication.
我得走了
Uh, I gotta go.
你得走了
You gotta go?
危险 广播
他得走了
He's gotta go.
对  抱歉
Yeah...sorry, um...
这很...抱歉
This was...sorry.
他跑出去这事你会记下来的  是吧
You're gonna write down that he ran out of here, aren't you?
肯定的
Yes.
趴下
Get down!
大家都没事吧
Everybody okay?
我不知道  肯定是颗哑弹
I don't know. Must've been a dud.
中城警局
一样的破坏代码  是同一个人
Same corrupted code. Same guy.
这个家伙精心设计
Someone very creatively
想要杀掉蒂姆·权和科特·韦弗
tried to kill Tim Kwon and Kurt Weaver.
权现在在哪儿
Where's Kwon now?
他跑出去了  给他吓傻了
He ran out of here scared out of his mind.
他连安保护卫小队都不想等
He wouldn't even wait for a protected escort.
但好消息是
But the good news is,
我找到了受害人之间的联系
I found a connection between our victims.
四年前  科特·韦弗和蒂姆·权
Four years ago, Kurt Weaver and Tim Kwon
与其他两个程序员在车库里创建了一个应用
created an app in their garage with two other programmers.
2014年南休斯顿地区经济贡献奖得主
一种名叫基尔戈的流氓软件
Some kind of malware called Kilgore.
然后他们把软件卖给了一家大型的科技公司
And then they sold it off to a big tech company.
所以他们就是这么赚钱的
So that's how they made their money.
我见过这人  他之前在这儿
I saw this guy. He was here.
拉姆齐·迪肯  看来我们找到超能力者了
Ramsey Deacon. Looks like we found our meta.
出于某些原因  他在追杀以前的小伙伴
And for some reason he's going after his old partners.
一部科技宅造软件的美剧
就好像《硅谷》的理查德发了疯
It's like "Silicon Valley" if Richard went nuts
要杀掉魔笛手的每一个人
and started killing everyone at Pied Piper.
另一个《硅谷》的主要人物
我感觉他更有无政府主义者吉尔弗约尔的气质
I feel like he's got more of a anarchist Gilfoyle vibe.
或许更像埃利希
Erlich, maybe.
听着  二位  我很开心你们能对自己
Look, guys, I love that we are so confident
理解坏人心理的能力这么有自信
in our ability to apprehend villains
还能扯这么远  但是别跑题啊
that we can have this debate, but, hi.
-她是谁  -她是希拉·阿娜妮
- What about her? - That's Sheila Agnani.
她现在算是个超厉害的科技大师了
She's, like, a big deal tech guru now.
迪肯下一个可能就会去杀她了
She could be next on Deacon's list.
我们肯定要去保护她
We'll definitely have to protect her.
对  我爸爸和沃利可以去保护她  对吧
Yeah, well, my dad and Wally can do that, right?
-这就去  -好极了
- I'm on it. - Great.
我继续研究代码
I'll keep working on the code.
-好  -心理治疗的事真对不起
- Sure. - Sorry about therapy.
没事  我告诉芬科尔医生
Oh, it's okay. I told Dr. Finkel
你有工作上有急事
that you had a work emergency.
也算是实话了
True. Kind of.
是  还有  她今天下午的预约取消了
Yeah, and she had a cancellation this afternoon,
所以我们应该去找她
so we should get over there.
可不要迟到啊
Don't wanna be late.
不会  当然
No--yeah.
我们回去吧...
Let's get back in there...
这人简直就是个活生生的电脑病毒啊
This guy is a living computer virus.
-这是个新代码  -看这段
- That's a new one. - Look at this code.
从电梯  到汽车
From the elevator, to the car,
再到炸弹机器人  这段代码一直在变
to the bomb robot, this code keeps changing...
但我想不通为什么
But I can't figure out why.
好了  我们别忘了这不只是数码病毒
Okay, we have to remember that it's not just digital.
这些代码是生物数字
It's bio-digital.
大多数有机病毒通过变异避免被杀死
Most organic viruses mutate to avoid being killed.
所以如果我们设法创造出数字抗体
So, if we managed to create digital antibodies,
就能阻止这个家伙
then we can shut this guy down.
太棒了
Oh, nice one!
你过来我太高兴了
I'm so glad you're here,
因为我真心  从我的内心深处
'cause I truly, deeply, from the bottom of my heart--
感到很抱歉  但我得取消我们的约会
I am sorry, but I'm gonna have to cancel our date.
如果你要用震波攻击我
If you're gonna vibe blast me,
我能自己选择地点吗
can I at least pick the spot?
没关系  西斯科
It's fine, Cisco.
-我理解  -你理解
- I get it. - You get it?
有什么不能理解的  你得工作  所以...
Yeah, what's not to get? You have to work, so...
我们的约会就取消吧
we will cancel our date.
祝你们好运  希望你们工作顺利
Well, good luck, you guys. I hope it works out.
这个女人太酷了
What a cool chick.
她真的很大度
She took that so well.
她没有
No. No, she didn't.
当一个女人说她理解你
When a girl says she gets it,
她真正的意思是她完全不能理解
what she really means is she doesn't get it at all.
把我搞糊涂了
I'm confused.
别  这很简单
Don't be. Very simple.
我的朋友  你有大麻烦了
You, my friend, are in so much trouble.
你就是注定要爱上
You just had to fall for the girl
这个穿着黑色连体皮衣的女人
in head-to-toe black leather, didn't you?
我回来了
We're back.
即便对我来说这都算快了
That was quick, even for me.
这是个内部笑话
Inside joke...so, yes.
抛开工作上的急事不说
Work emergency aside,
我隐隐觉得
I have a sneaking suspicion
你不太愿意呆在这里  巴里
that you'd rather be somewhere else, Barry.
不是  不是  我
No, no. I--um...
我想说我们
I mean, we do have a...
工作上确实有件急事需要处理
big work thing that we're dealing with.
很重要的事
It's important.
但这也很重要
Yeah, but so is this.
如果我们不能达成共识的话  巴里
You know, if we're not on the same page, Barry,
会有人死的
people could die.
只是打个比喻
Metaphorically.
别
No. No, no.
别憋着
Don't hold back.
看着爱瑞丝  看着她的眼睛
Turn to Iris, look her in the eyes,
告诉她你想对她说的话
and tell her what you wanted to say.
我不知道
I don't know-- uh, well...
我
I...
我已经为今天早上的事道歉了
I said I was sorry about this morning.
爱瑞丝
Iris.
看着巴里  告诉他
Turn to Barry. Talk to him.
不只是今天早上的事
It's not just this morning, Barry.
你那天没和我商量
You cancelled training
就取消了训练
the other day without asking me.
什么训练
Training?
-游泳  -为了马拉松比赛
- Swimming. - For a marathon.
实际上是铁人三项比赛
It's a...triathlon.
我不觉得取消训练
Anyway, I didn't think cancelling training
是什么大事
was that big of a deal.
但是婚礼安排也是
Yeah, but you made all those wedding plans too
你没有问过我就做了决定
and you didn't consult me.
我想做一个合格的未婚夫
I was trying to be a good fiance.
我以为大部分新娘都会高兴看到
Yeah, but I'd think most brides would be happy
她们的未婚夫参与到婚礼安排中
that their future spouse cared about helping with the wedding.
这是好事  不是吗
That is a good thing, right?
我不知道  我是说  我觉得
Look, I don't know. I mean, I guess
过去这几天里我们两个之间有点误会
our wires have gotten crossed a few times the last few days,
但我认为还没有上升到危机的程度
but I think that hardly rises to the level of a crisis.
我们两个一起经历了那么多
After everything we've been through together,
我们两个是巴里和爱瑞丝
you and me, we're Barry and Iris.
是模范情侣
We're the gold standard.
-我很爱你  -那你怎么可以离开我
- I am so in love-- - Then how could you leave me?
你离开了我  你丢下我
You left me, Barry. You just left me.
让我自己一个人在那里
Standing there, alone.
你怎么可以那样做
How could you do that?
所有的监听设备就位
All the listening devices are in place.
注意一切动静
Keep your ears open.
必须得保证她的安全
Gotta make sure she's safe.
怎么了  我喜欢朋克音乐
What? I like punk music.
蒂姆  怎么回事
Tim? What the hell, man?
你不能就这样来我家
You can't just come into my house.
因为你不回我电话  我真的需要
'Cause you wouldn't return my calls. I really need--
是因为你喜欢我吗  放手吧  蒂姆
Is this about your weird crush? Let it go, Tim.
-我们两个不可能  -希拉  听着
- We are not happening. - Sheila, listen.
迪肯来找我们了
Deacon's coming for us.
他要为我们对他做的事报复我们
He wants payback for what we did to him.
我们对他做什么了
What did we do to him?
科特把我们间的所有联系都从网上抹去了
Kurt scrubbed any connection between us from the net,
在所有人看来我们都是清白的
so as far as the world's concerned, we're innocent.
但我们不是
But we're not.
我当时就不该听你的
I should've never let you talk me
让我做这个
into going along with this.
现在科特死了
And now Kurt's dead.
迪肯杀了他
Deacon killed him.
他没有
He did not.
不错
Oh, yes. He did.
这房子不错
Oh, this is a nice house.
花了多少钱  一千万吗
How much do you pay for it? 10 mil?
咱们谈一谈  我们能让一切回到正轨
Let's talk about this. We can make it right.
住口  蒂姆
Shut up, Tim.
你本来也可以拥有这一切的
You could've had all this too.
这也有可能是你的
This is could've been yours.
基尔戈是我的主意
Kilgore was my idea.
你们仨偷走了
And you three stole it away from me.
总得有人这么干
Somebody had to.
否则  那就可能只是个
Otherwise, it would've just been a halfway clever idea
夭折在某人车库里的好主意罢了
that died in someone's garage.
希拉
Sheila.
不  我不会道歉的
No, I'm not going to apologize
因为过了四年
because after four years,
你终于有点胆量了
you finally found some balls.
我有了其他东西
I found something else.
和我家人  在麻省理工
Something I never had with my family,
和你们在一起时从没有过的
or at MIT, or with any of you.
真的吗  那是什么
Really? And what was that?
能力
Power.
你不会还有糖尿病吧
Oh, you're not still diabetic, are you?
那些新型的电脑控制的胰岛素泵
Those new computer-controlled insulin pumps
可真是健康救星啊
are a real life saver.
但过量  就会致命了
Way too much insulin-- well, that can be lethal.
该如何灭了你呢
How should we kill you?
他害她低血糖休克了
He put her in insulin shock.
葡萄糖
Glucose.
迪肯把他带走了
Deacon took him.
他带走了蒂姆
He took Tim.
找不到迪肯和权  面部识别和
No sign of Deacon or Kwon on facial recognition,
交通监控都找不到
traffic cameras--nothing.
我们甚至都不知道权是不是还活着
We don't even know if Kwon's still alive.
我们得快
We gotta move fast.
你俩去哪了
Where were you two?
-干洗店  -婚礼  干洗店
- Dry cleaners. - Wedding... cleaners.
干洗店
Dry cleaners.
西斯科
Cisco?
那些抗体你研究得怎么样了
Where are you with those bio-digital antibodies?
毫无进展
I'm nowhere.
事实上  不
Actually, no-- you know what?
我进展到某处了  我进狗窝了[丢脸]
I am somewhere. I'm in the doghouse.
很明显是盆状的狗窝
Apparently the pan-dimensional doghouse.
我不知道这狗窝
I don't know if this doghouse
有没有门或者窗  如果有
has a door or window, but if it did,
我要跳出来
I'd be jumping out of it!
没事  我去和他谈谈
It's okay. I'll go talk to him.
都疯了吗
Has everybody lost their minds?
她肯定以为我不在乎她
She must think I'm blowing her off.
但我只是想做好我的工作
But I'm just trying to do my job.
估计再约这个词在地球十九不存在
I guess the word "Reschedule" doesn't exist on Earth 19.
我大胆猜一下
Okay, I'm gonna go out on a limb here and guess that
你不能集中精力搞研究的原因是
the reason you can't focus on the science is because
你担心你和吉普赛的关系
you're so worried about what's going on with Gypsy.
不好意思  我听不到
I'm sorry, I didn't hear anything you said.
但我觉得我明白了
But I-I think I figured it out.
我觉得我不能集中精力
I think I can't focus on anything
就是因为吉普赛的事儿
'cause of this whole Gypsy situation.
我觉得  我得和她谈谈
I'm--I think I'm just gonna have to talk to her.
好主意
What a great idea.
怎么了  西斯科
What's up, Cisco?
你生我的气
You're mad at me.
我说了没事
I said it was fine.
不不不
No, no, no.
第一条  女孩说没事  就是有事
Rule number one, when a girl says it's fine, it's not fine.
赞同
Amen!
我马上走
I'm gonna go.
第二条
Rule number two,
不能放最喜欢的人鸽子
you don't blow off a date with your favorite person.
这天已经过去  让我补偿你好吗
The day got away from me. Let me make it up to you, okay?
明晚再约好吗
Date night tomorrow?
不  西斯科  必须是今天
No, Cisco. It... it had to be today.
为什么
Why today?
因为今天是111节
- Because today is One-One-One Day.
1什么
One-what-what-what?
111节
It's One-One-One Day.
那是啥
What is that?
111节在我的地球是
One-One-One Day on my Earth is...
是你和你最爱的人
is the day that you celebrate with the one...
一起过的
with the one you love, all right?
在那天  一个人加另一个人  等于
It's when one soul, plus one soul, equals...
一个完整的灵魂
one soul.
这...  好傻啊
That is... so sappy.
是  是很傻
Yes, it is sappy.
而且这很愚蠢和呆笨
And it is stupid and schmoopy.
但你就是有办法
But there is something about you that--
让我做愚蠢和呆笨的事
it makes me wanna do stupid, schmoopy things.
我讨厌"呆笨"这个词和用这个词的人
And I hate the word "Schmoop" and people who use it.
那是你对说过最甜蜜和
Well, that is the sweetest and angriest thing
最愤怒的话
you've ever said to me.
你为什么没对我说过
Why didn't you just tell me that?
因为我很尴尬  西斯科
Because I was embarrassed, Cisco.
知道吗  还是算了吧
So, you know what? Let's just forget about it.
因为一天结束了  而且我真的想忘了
Because the day is already over and I would really like
我提起过这件事
to forget that I ever brought this up--
不不不
No, no, no.
我不会忘记的  好吗
I will not forget it, okay?
你对我很重要
You are important to me.
如果111天对你很重要
And if One-One-One Day is important to you...
One-One-One.
我明白了
That's it.
我得走了
I gotta go.
他好像不知道自己死定了
It's like he doesn't know that he's a dead man.
我不知道为什么我认为我们不需要
I don't know why I thought that we didn't have
谈论发生了什么事
to talk about what happened.
你很开心我回来了
You were so happy I was back.
我很开心
I am happy.
你是我的一切
You're everything to me.
听着
Look...
我得向我的家人和朋友解释
I had to explain to our friends and family
为什么他们预留我们的结婚日出来了
why they had a save-the-date for our wedding
但却没收到请帖
but no invitation.
我得不断为你为什么离开说谎
I had to constantly lie about why you were gone.
你不知道他们给我的表情
You don't know the looks people gave me
他们知道我说的不是实话
because they knew that wasn't the truth.
你知道他们怎么想我们的事吗
You know, what they must've thought about us.
你知道我怎么想我们的事吗
What it made me think about us.
爱瑞丝
Iris...
我不想离开你的
It's not like I wanted to leave you.
我得在大家面前显得很勇敢
I had to put on a brave face for everyone,
但我内心却在撕裂
but it was killing me inside.
我没跟你谈的其中一个原因
And I think part of why I didn't talk it through
就是...  我害怕
with you is... I was afraid.
我害怕你会让我留下
I was afraid that you would tell me to stay.
我就无法坚定地不照办
And I wouldn't have been strong enough not to.
巴里  你不问我  你怎么知道
Barry, how do you know what I'm gonna say
我会怎么说
if you don't ask me?
我要帮助你
I am here to help you.
尤其是在一切好像都迷失了
Especially when everything seems lost.
但你得让我帮忙
But you have to let me.
有时不只是我们或队伍
But sometimes it's not about us, or the team.
有时整座城市的重量
Sometimes the weight of the whole city
都压在我肩上  必须由我来背负
falls on my shoulders, and it's up to me to carry it.
我是闪电侠
I'm the Flash.
这就是你不明白的地方
See, that's what you don't get.
当我把这戒指戴在手指上时
When I put this ring on my finger,
就不再是我和你了
it wasn't just about you or me anymore.
而是我们
It was about us.
你不是闪电侠  巴里
You are not the Flash, Barry.
我们是
We are.
各位
Guys.
我们需要你们  是迪肯的事
We need you. It's about Deacon.
我要忏悔一件事
I have something to confess.
我  科特·韦弗和希拉·阿娜妮
Kurt Weaver, Sheila Agnani, and I--
一起偷了拉姆齐·迪肯的基尔戈恶意程式
we stole the Kilgore malware program from Ramsey Deacon.
我们卖了几十亿
We sold it for billions.
但这是他的创意
But it was all his idea.
我们发家了  他却一无所得
We got rich. And he got nothing.
所以迪肯才要那样报复
I guess that explains why Deacon's got such a vendetta.
西斯科  你可以追踪视频直播的信号吗
Cisco, if he's livestreaming, can you track the signal?
大概两秒钟就好
In, like, two seconds.
哥喜欢拥有自己的卫星
Papa loves having his own satellite.
找到他后你们打算怎么做
What are you gonna do when you find him?
-用这个攻击他  -那是什么
- Hit him with this. - What is that?
迪肯的超能力是由
Deacon's powers are derived
他DNA的二进制码衍生出来的
from the binary code in his DNA.
所以我们合成了一个
So, we created a compound encoded
由1和0组成的数字串编码
with a numerical string pattern of ones and zeros
以倒转编码的顺序
to invert the order of the code.
1变成0  反之亦然
Ones become zeros, and vice versa.
1加1加1
One plus one plus one.
好  我们准备就绪
All right, we're on it.
找到位置就发给我们
Send us the location once you have it.
-好吧  -开干
- Okay. - Let's do it.
现在你知道真相了
And now you know the truth.
我们偷了拉姆齐·迪肯的基尔戈
We stole Kilgore from Ramsey Deacon.
他是真正的受害者
He is the real victim.
很好
Good.
你忘了一件事
You forgot one thing.
什么
What?
你没跟会想念你的人道别
You didn't say good-bye to anyone who's gonna miss you.
你有玩过叉骨吗  蒂姆
You ever play wishbone, Tim?
他和其他人毁了我的生活
He and the others destroyed my life!
我知道你感到很委屈  迪肯
Listen, I know you feel wronged, Deacon,
但你没有权利夺走他的性命
but that doesn't give you a right to take his life.
我察觉到你战衣里的科技了
I smell technology in your suit.
里面有什么
What have you got in there?
糟糕
Oh, crap.
我不能动
I can't move.
武器系统上线
Weapon system online.
正在瞄准
Targeting.
快跑
Run.
叫我基尔戈
Call me Kilgore.
巴里  怎么回事
Barry? What's happening?
是迪肯  他对我的战衣做了什么
It's Deacon, he's done something with my suit.
远程访问完成
Remote access complete.
你把你的声音放进巴里的战衣了
You put your voice in Barry's suit?
总得有个人
Well, it had to be somebody
而且我的声音能令人宽心
and my voice is soothing.
你到底给这战衣放入了多少科技
How much tech did you put in this suit?
很多
So much.
过去几年我其实是
I've actually always been a huge Flash fan
闪电侠的大粉丝
these past couple of years.
但这就像是有个巨型玩具人
But this is like having a giant action figure.
拒绝访问
可恶  他把我锁在我自己的程序外面了
Frack me, he's locked me out of my own programming.
做点什么
Do something.
巴里  远离他
Barry, get away from him.
这也许能减弱他对你的控制
It might lessen his technopathic hold over you.
我不能
I can't!
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
有人在听吗
Someone listening in?
不能那样
Can't have that.
巴里  巴里
Barry? Barry.
他的通讯设备下线了
His comms are offline.
你有去纤颤器
You have a defibrillator.
我让你的心脏停止吧
How about I stop your heart?
喂
Hello?
你收到一个由你付费电话
You have a collect call from...
各位  帮我
Guys, help me!
我们愿意付费
We accept the charges.
战衣还在发疯
The suit's still freaking out.
好吧  脱掉它
Well, get it off!
不行  我不能脱掉它
Nope-- yeah, I can't get it off.
那就是死锁的功能
That would be the deadlock function.
我造这个是以防他被坏蛋打晕
I built it in case he ever got knocked out
身份也不会曝露
so a bad guy wouldn't reveal his identity.
在那时这似乎是个聪明的主意
It seemed like a smart idea at the time.
启动浮动模式
Flotation mode activated.
什么
What?
他到底要救生筏做什么  西斯科
What the hell does he need a raft for, Cisco?
他在水上跑
He runs on water.
他可能会在那失速
He might lose his speed out there.
他能怎么样  他可能会溺水
What's he gonna do then? He might drown.
你为什么不能直接在战衣里加氧气筒
You couldn't just put an oxygen tank in the suit?
那是个好主意
That's a good idea.
怎么这东西还完好无损
How is this thing still intact?
西斯科
Cisco!
启动巴贝尔协议
Babel Protocol activated.
什么
What?
什么是巴贝尔协议
What's Babel Protocol?
我为什么在倒计时
Why am I ticking?
这是自毁程序
It's the self-destruct sequence.
-什么  -自毁
- What? - Self-destruct?
我很抱歉  我们以前没面对过
I-I'm sorry, have we not faced
邪恶版的巴里吗
an evil version of Barry before?
我的错
My mistake!
我要怎么阻止
Well, how do I stop it?
该死
Hell no.
天啊
Oh, God.
西斯科  我们一定能做点什么
Cisco, there must be something we can do.
只要这东西还有电  我们无能为力
Not as long as this thing's powered up.
赶紧的  赶紧的
Come on, come on!
巴里  你能听到我说话吗
Barry? Can you hear me?
爱瑞丝
Iris!
我很抱歉  好吗  我很抱歉
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
告诉我该怎么做  我就照做
Just tell me what to do, and I'll do it.
你要抛出一道闪电
You need to throw a lightning bolt.
抛向哪
At what?
你自己
Yourself.
你要他做什么
You want him to do what?
这可能会造成战衣短路  让他重获控制
It might short the suit out, give him back control.
或者可能提前触发自毁
Or it might set off the self-destruct early.
或者可能造成他心脏停止
Or it might stop his heart.
巴里
Barry?
巴里  听我说  好吗
Barry, you need to listen to me, okay?
我们能做到
We can do this.
好
Okay.
不  我相信你  爱瑞丝
No, I trust you, Iris.
那就跑  巴里
Then run, Barry.
跑
Run.
巴里
Barry?
蒂姆
Oh, Tim.
我知道我有世界上最酷的超能力  但
I know I have the coolest superpower ever, but...
我有点累
I'm kinda tired.
你好  俏女郎
Hello, gorgeous.
在地球一  今天我们庆祝111天
Here on Earth 1, we celebrate One-One-One Day today,
虽然我完全不知道这个日子的意义
even though I have zero idea what that means,
或者你地球的任何假日的意义
or what any of your Earth's holidays mean.
我简直不敢相信你庆祝
I mean, I literally cannot believe you celebrate
圣沙奎尔·奥尼尔日这种日子
a day called Saint Shaquille O'Neal's Day.
你们有穿着红衣的魔法精灵
You guys have a magical elfling in a red suit
闯进你屋里吃你的饼干
that breaks into your house and eats your cookies.
其实  他是精灵们的老大
Actually, he's the boss of the elves,
也许你该先做个调查
so, like, maybe do your research before.
我知道的是你对我有多特别
What I do know is how special you are to me.
还有我昨天
And how sorry I am
不能陪你我有多抱歉
that I didn't get to spend yesterday with you.
我猜你忙着去抓疯狂的杀手
Well, I guess you were busy catching a deranged killer.
宝贝  我们总是忙着抓疯狂的杀手
Baby, we are always catching a deranged killer around here.
没错
True.
我总是会补偿你的
I will always make it up to you.
我是认真的
I mean that.
你只要让我知道这很重要
You just gotta let me know when it's this important.
我会的
I will.
好吧
All right, then.
准备好呆笨了吗
Ready to get your schmoopy on?
我的亲呆笨游戏可强了
'Cause, you know, my schmoopy game is real strong.
这很残忍和不寻常
This is cruel and unusual.
没有电子书阅读器  我在这要怎么生存
How will I survive in here without my Kindle?
你不能再碰任何电子设备
You ain't touching anything electronic ever again.
你跟外面的世界之间
There's three layers of signal-dampening walls
有三层信号屏蔽的墙
between you and the world.
没有电线  甚至没有电灯泡
No wiring. Not even a lightbulb.
现今到处都是科技
There's technology everywhere these days.
好吧  我们只有一个问题问你
That's fine, we just have one question for you.
四年前粒子加速器爆炸时
That particle accelerator explosion four years ago--
你住在硅谷
you were living in Silicon Valley.
那晚你不在这里
So, if you weren't here that night,
你怎么获得超能力的
how did you get your powers?
你不会相信的
Oh, you're not gonna believe it.
但真的有这么回事
It really was something, though.
现实生活改变者
A real life changer.
你俩想知道最棒的是什么吗
And do you two wanna know the best part?
不是只有我一个
I wasn't the only one.
祝好运  先生们
So, good luck, gentlemen.
看来中城要忙起来了
Think Central City's about to have its hands full.
谢谢你让我们见囚犯  沃夫监狱长
Thank you for letting us see the prisoner, Warden Wolfe.
乐意效劳  你们得到你们需要的东西了吗
Oh, my pleasure. Did you get what you needed?
-应该是的  -好吧  别担心
- We think so. - Well, not to worry.
这个叫基尔戈的人不会离开的
This so-called Kilgore isn't going anywhere.
我们会看好他的
We'll take good care of him.
如果迪肯不是从威尔斯的
How is it possible that Deacon's a meta
粒子加速器爆炸时获取超能力
if he didn't get his powers
那他怎么可能变成超能力者的呢
from Wells' particle accelerator blowing up?
不管是怎么回事  我们会搞明白的
However it happened, we will figure it out,
而且我们会准备好的
and we will be ready.
等西斯科把你战衣上的科技都取出来
After Cisco gets all that tech out of your suit.
你当闪电侠不需要那些奇特小配件
You don't need fancy gadgets to be the Flash.
-你是闪电侠  -不
- You are the Flash. - No.
我们是
We are.
我错过了什么吗
Did I miss something?
我童年最喜欢的作品之一
Ah, one of my childhood favorites.
舒伯特的《第八交响曲(未完成)》
Schubert's "Unfinished Eighth Symphony."
不过现在已经完成了
Unfinished until now.
不是吧
You didn't.
当我熟悉了他作品的大体时
It was surprisingly simple to extrapolate
推算接下来的乐章
the remaining movements once I familiarized myself
就变得惊人得简单
with the body of his work.
他的所有六百份作品吗
All 600 of his works?
我今天起得早
I woke up early this morning.
你有新情况要汇报吗
Do you have an update?
已找到对像一的所在位置
Subject One has been located.
他很安全
He's safe.
此刻被关在
Locked up in the meta-human wing
铁山监狱的超能力者区
at Iron Heights as we speak.
他就在你需要他的地方
He's right where you wanted him.
我们现在怎么做
What do we do now?
找出其他人
Now we find the others.